<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">RotorControl</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="connect_string">Connect to Remote Rotor</string>
    <string name="get_heading">Get Heading</string>
    <string name="heading">Set Heading: </string>
    <string name="rotate">Rotate Antenna</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string name="ip_address">Host Name or IP Address</string>
    <string name="provide_ip_address">Please provide the host name or IP address of the machine which has rotctld running.</string>
    <string name="port">Port Number</string>
    <string name="provide_port_number">Please provide the port number of the rotctld process.</string>
    <string name="help_contents">This GUI application works with the 
           open source hamlib project.  ( http://hamlib.sourceforge.net )\n
           You need a rotor that can be controlled via serial port and 
           a computer that is connected to that rotor controller via 
           the serial port.  This computer must also be connected to 
           the local area network and running the hamlib rotctld 
           rotor control daemon.  The rotor must support the 
           get_position and set_position commands.  This app 
           connects via the network to that daemon (usually on port 4533), and 
           sends and gets the heading.  At present, it works 
           for azimuth only.  \nFor setup information on the server, see the man page.  It is available at 
           ( http://manpages.ubuntu.com/manpages/lucid/man8/rotctld.8.html ).
            \n  Once you have the rotctld running on the
            server you start this app on your phone and hit the "Connect to Server" 
            button.  It will disappear, and you will have the option
            of getting the present heading of the rotor (in degrees) with the "Get Heading"
            button or setting a new heading with the "Heading" text entry
            field.  The rotor will rotate to the new heading (which is apporoximately
            what you asked for in the text field by typing in a bearing in degrees). 
            A CDE or HyGain rotor generally turns at about one revolution per
            minute, but to get closer to your specified heading, the rotor will
            seek with some controllers (like the Heathkit Intellirotor) for a while longer.
            You will know it is finished when you get a new heading on the
            screen.  If you wish you can quit this app soon after setting the new
            heading, and the rotation will still complete.</string>
    <string name="help_heading_contents">Help</string>
    <string name="degrees">degrees</string>
    <string name="map_View">Great Circle Map</string>

</resources>